[{"answer": "You'd meet doctors, lawyers", "docId": "out-of-sight.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "We don't get to talk much any more", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Ever seen an uncut diamond, Studs? They look like plain old rocks", "docId": "out-of-sight.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "My point is, that's probably what you're gonna end up with", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I believe it.  You've ruined a nin", "docId": "out-of-sight.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "The idea of going after guys like you appealed to me", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Who, my friend?  Yeah.  He's a good guy. Back when we jailed together, he'd call his sister every week without fail.  She's a bor", "docId": "out-of-sight.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " One I gave him, yeah.  Fuck..", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Have you ever shot a man?  How many times have you been primary through the door", "docId": "out-of-sight.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You have to know what you're talking about", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " What are you thinking about", "docId": "out-of-sight.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Tell you what, you're a good girl, you might get another one for Christmas", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I can just picture that, a cute girl like you following sli", "docId": "out-of-sight.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Why?  You think he might tell you where I am", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "One last score, that the idea?  Move to some island", "docId": "out-of-sight.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Whatta you mean  make it an island", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "They didn't  me anything, they asked questions", "docId": "out-of-sight.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I know a my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "But you spoke to him on the phone", "docId": "out-of-sight.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "He called the day he escaped", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You did work for my friend, right", "docId": "out-of-sight.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "You were his what, his box", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " Take the radio, stay down here in the lobby, watch the elevator", "docId": "out-of-sight.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You can go wait out in the car, you want to", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Me", "docId": "out-of-sight.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Can I do what", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "You'd be surprised what all you can get, you ask for it the right way", "docId": "out-of-sight.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "No?  Where do you keep it, my friend?  I'm talking about all those uncut diamonds you told my friend about", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Of course not", "docId": "out-of-sight.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Doesn't have to figure out shit.  You him you keep 'em at your house", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " That was some shit, huh", "docId": "out-of-sight.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Yeah, my friend, why you have to do that to that poor girl", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I report to the that place, first thing they're gonna do is ask me to go get some coffee", "docId": "out-of-sight.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "No, I didn't know that", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Is that how you think of yourself", "docId": "out-of-sight.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "A girl", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I don't think it works if we're somebody else.  You know what I mean?  my friend and my friend, my friend, what do they know about anything", "docId": "out-of-sight.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "It's not a game.  Something you play", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": " You know they gonna set us up", "docId": "out-of-sight.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "But you still think you can get the diamonds fore they do", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": " Well, if it isn't the Ripper hisself", "docId": "out-of-sight.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Where you been hiding, my friend", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "What's it mean,", "docId": "out-of-sight.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "The flight", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "The flight", "docId": "out-of-sight.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "You were at that place, huh", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "That time", "docId": "out-of-sight.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Yeah.  That was the ninth", "qsentId": 48}]